<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="Hello">Hello World, Click Me!</string>
    <string name="ApplicationName">Leonardo</string>
  <string name="rule1">
    <b>
      Use the finger to put the active card on the board.\n
      The game begins with 72 cards that gradually run out.\n
      Cards can appear in <u>3 different shapes</u>.
    </b>
  </string>
  <string name="rule2">
    <b>
      Cards can appear in <u>3 different colors</u>.
    </b>
  </string>
  <string name="rule3">
    <b>
      Cards can appear in <u>4 different quantities</u>.
    </b>
  </string>
  <string name="rule4">
    <b>
      <u>The object of the game</u>:\n
      To position the cards in the matrix in a way that creates\n
      as many commonalities as possible.
      A line that has at least one
      commonality will disappear.\n
      <u>Same color</u>
    </b>
  </string>
  <string name="rule5">
    <b>
      <u>Same shape</u>
    </b>
  </string>
  <string name="rule6">
    <b>
      <u>Same quantity</u>
    </b>
  </string>
  <string name="rule7">
    <b>
      <u>The challenge</u>:\n
      Achieving one or even two commonalties is pretty\n
      easy, but the real challenge strive for multiple\n
      commonalties. The best tactic is the "Tripod"\n
      <u>The Tripod</u>:\n
      The tripod tactic lets you close at least 3
      commonalties at the same time.
    </b>\n
  </string>
  <string name="rule8">
    <b>
      <u>Here is how</u>:
      This Tripod is closed with one red cherry card.\n
      1. Focus on the quantity and place the cards in their columns.\n
      2. Leave the top left square empty and wait for a "One" to close the Tripod.\n
      Cleaning up To create multiple commonalties,\n
      you often need to gamble and wait for the right card.\n
      A card that doesnot support the Tripod should be placed in the blank zone.\n
      As the matrix gets full, and a Tripod is NOT achieved,\n
      you need to abandon the Tripod tactic and clean the matrix anyway you can.\n
      This will help you get ready for the next attempt at a Tripod.\n
      <u>Improvisation</u>:\n
      Although the Tripod is the most promising tactic, you will\n
      need to open your eyes (and your mind) to special situations\n
      where a different tactic should be used. \n
      You will become aware of it as you play.\n
      The game ends when the matrix is full,\n
      or when you run out of cards.
    </b>\n
  </string>
  <string name="rule9">
    <b>
      <u>You are ready to play !</u>
    </b>
  </string>

</resources>
